END
When you've got to play smart
Imagine if the chance the wise will take it all
Every I see the hell is that you're gone
So I can't be good, that I'm gone
I'm going to run the universe of thoughts
I'm going to die, don't move
You're right when all is done
You're right, it's gonna break
I've already seen the time
We're shotting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,決勝とした光を
今こそ解放する
We're shotting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,決戦闘 栄光のそう
核心と運命を始めよう
So, what now?
Hero, you are not like most mortals
And I believe you may even have stood a slim chance
Of defeating the demon lord
But we'll never know because your journey ends here
Wait, are you going to fight him without your monster buddy?
You misunderstand me, this old body would be no match for the hero
Which is why I would like to show you something
It's horrible
You may recognize them from a previous encounter
These are, in fact, the heads of my wife and young son
A sad but necessary measure to ensure your defeat
My next step requires their deaths, the entire village, and my own
The ultimate sacrifice must be made to invoke the most powerful summoning magic in the world
I call on the hyper-conceptual reaper Crowsday Thanatos to manifest
I don't think he's going to make it
Rista, open up a portal to the divine realm
What? You want me to do that now?
I don't see a portal opening
So it's hyper-conceptual because you can't read the stats or what?
Like, it's just a bunch of gobbledygook
Hmm, I can't make any sense out of his stats either
Do you think it's using fake-out?
No, doesn't seem like it
I'm pretty sure those are just its regular stats
I don't know what that means
It means that thing's going to kick our ass
Have a taste of my double wind blade
Got him!
Where's the damn portal?
Why? You just slashed it up!
Whoa, now there's two of those things?
How is that possible?
It just landed a hit on Seiya?
Maximum Inferno!
Rista, move your ass and open the portal
Oh, yeah, on it!
Master!
Ah!
Toss them in like he was taking out the trash
No thanks, I'm far too delicate for-
Ah!
Do you really have to kick me through the portal like that?
Oh no, are you okay?
I think I'll survive, but I'm hurt pretty badly
I can fix you up
Show me where it hurts
Fine
Uh, is it one of those things where it feels worse than it looks?
Earlier I was at 300,000 HP
This wound took me down another hundred
You're such a baby!
I won't fight unless I start out at max HP
So heal me
Jeez
Do you need a diaper change too?
So what was the deal with that thing back there?
That was crazy, wasn't it?
It goes against the rules of living things and magic and all the things!
We need to come up with a strategy
It can't get us here, so let's figure that out before we go back
No way
It's breaking through the dimensional barrier
That freaking thing is unstoppable!
There's gotta be some kind of way to take it down, right?
All right, Saya, I'm sure you've already figured out its weakness
So you want to share that info with us?
No clue
I have absolutely no idea how to beat it
If Saya's at a loss, we're totally screwed!
What do we do? We break it out here!
Hold it right there, fellow demon!
Nice!
Now we've got some celebrity god power backing us up!
Wretched beast!
Prepare to feel the divine power of the gods!
Tornado chips!
ROARING BLACK STUGGER!
I stopped hugging!
All their attacks didn't even face it!
Hey, Rista!
Huh?
That dirty cat coward!
You're not cautious, you're chicken!
You can't run away from everything, you know!
Ah!
Hey, guys, it's still following us!
Keep running!
Hey, y'all! Wait for us!
You don't belong here, demon!
For your trespass, you face the invincible fist of art!
Oh, my face!
Game over, man!
I am Kibono!
Now feel the swift and humiliating power of my divine hundred and slap!
And you're walking past me!
God damn it!
Somebody's getting rambunctious.
Hey there!
Feast your eyes on this!
It's my latest creation of culinary art!
And I'm...
Out of the way, lady!
No!
My cake!
I am so glad to see you're back!
Do me a solid and deal with that thing that's chasing us.
Then you can deal with me, if you know what I mean.
Oh, I know.
You're messing with the wrong hunk, pal!
Now!
You're gonna pay!
Get you some, goth goddess!
Completely useless, like I expected.
You'll strike her along just to throw her away!
This sucks!
We can't run away from this thing forever, you know!
But what else can we even do?
Unclench, will ya?
Obviously you have no idea how to beat this crank!
I don't, but I do have a plan ready just in case we come across an enemy who I don't know how to beat.
A backup backup plan.
Huh?
She may look like some kind of post-apocalyptic S&M reject, but she's an artist at heart.
She's probably painting on top of the temple roof right now.
I don't know who you mean!
Wait.
Valkyrie?
You think she's gonna fight this mega-stalker on our behalf?
Kind of.
There's no chance in hell she'll agree to it if we just go up and ask her.
Therefore...
All right, just what I wanted.
Well, it's on!
No freaking way.
I've been working on that piece forever, and I was almost done!
Are you ready?
I'm gonna paint my next picture with your blood!
You should get back.
How do you know?
Yes!
Holy!
Or maybe I'll smash you into a million little pieces and use them to make a mosaic instead!
Feel my shattered break!
The hell?
Is it a ghost?
Well, that's fine by me.
Try this.
It's my fourth Valkyrie-sia.
Eat my astral break!
Uh-oh.
Even the strongest goddess in the divine realm can't stop him?
Buy his charm!
Grant this order!
She just unleashed her suppressed divine power, so it's about to get real ugly up in here!
She's totally maxed out!
Huh.
The other gods all seem pretty weak compared to her.
But, to be perfectly honest, I've been really unimpressed with everyone here up until now.
Time for Omega Valkyrie.
Gate of Valhalla.
What'd she do?
I have no idea!
Well, that's a super creepy move.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I found you!
Oh!
It's not every day that I use an inescapable, destructive technique that transcends the very fabric of reality.
But sometimes you gotta kick it up a notch.
Oh, are you okay?
Don't come near me, Rista!
It's happening.
Here goes.
What's happening?
Ah!
She's got flattery!
Gate of Valhalla uses the caster's life force as a catalyst.
That kind of boss move would definitely rip a human into bloody ribbons.
How can I help you?
That's the stuff, baby. I could get used to this.
Oh, yeah, right there.
Is your team a serenade?
So the order you activated wasn't to use your technique.
It was to deal with the recoil afterwards.
Yep, to make sure I bounce back.
Bye now.
Since you're the one who brought that monster up here and ruined my painting,
you're the one who's going to have to pay the toll,
which is going to cost you one handful of bare boobage.
Your own bare boobage?
Boop pro quo. Awkward. Pick one.
Oh, thank you.
Maybe under that cold, prickly shell, you're a man who'll fight for my honor.
Or maybe he can't stand the thought of someone else having extra fine, divine, dirty, touchy-feely time.
That's not how you get to second base!
All this time, you were the one for me.
Take me back to your place right now and train my brains out.
You want more training?
I mean, I know you like to be ready for anything, but we still have a job to do.
And we're going to do it.
But the foes keep getting stronger, so I should, too.
You can't pull off the kinds of crazy things that Valkyrie can.
If you even tried that Gate of Valhalla move, it'd turn you into spaghetti!
Little Miss Firm Cheeks is right.
There's no way a regular human could learn a Valkyrie-ja in the first place.
Well, I'm not a regular human.
You don't give up, do you?
I know you don't think about anything but training, but you can't even imagine the kind of spanking I'd give you.
If you whip that out, you'd better use it.
Please stop.
I can take what you got.
Oh, so you like it rough.
Yeah, because I need someone who's going to make me work for it.
All right, then, if you think you can take it.
But listen closely.
There's no way I'm teaching you how to do Gate of Valhalla.
Teach me something else.
Be at my place in ten minutes.
Uh, they're talking about training, right?
Is it okay with you if we go back to Aria's?
I really want to pick up where I left off.
Fine with me.
Go and have fun.
Thank you!
I guess you do need to learn some new destruction moves.
Not like we have much choice now.
I mean, the ultimate sword and legendary armor are out of the picture.
Like they say back in your world, this is really some hardcore kind of sitch we've stepped in, isn't it?
Whining about it isn't going to help.
So I picked up a piece of legendary armor.
Is that a chunk of adamantite the terrible turtle thing was stacking on?
It's not enough for armor, but I can use it to synthesize.
I'll call it adamantitor, the indestructible sword.
It may not work against the final boss, but it's the best sword there is right now.
Amazing work, Saya!
Way to make that lemonade!
You're the best!
Get off me, Rista.
Aw, you don't have to be shy.
I said get off of me.
You're carrying around my hair.
So I know you're a little sweet on me.
Listen.
I'm right, yeah?
You're ripe.
You're really stinky.
Seriously?
What do you mean?
Like what kind of smell is it anyway?
Hot garbage.
I have to go and take a bath right this minute before I die and then come back because I can't die!
Just go bathe.
I'm going over to Valkyrie's.
Hey, Circeus.
About time for you, too?
Couldn't just walk around the rest of the day covered in cake, could I?
The whole idea was for it to go in my face, not get smeared all over it.
That's fair.
Was it any good?
No, of course it wasn't any damn good.
It was way too salty.
It tasted like tears.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
Hey, that reminds me.
Ishtar was looking for you earlier.
Do you know what she wanted to talk about?
If I had to guess, I'd say it was about that demon you let in.
Like I'm 99% sure.
Ugh, I'm going to have to see her smelling all funky.
Well, Rista, I'm glad you stopped by.
Hey, look.
I'm sorry about that whole Reaper drama.
Oh, don't be silly.
That was not your fault, dear.
Besides, Valkyrie took care of it, didn't she?
It's not even an issue.
Then why were you looking for me?
It appears that the last of the four heavenly kings is making a move down on Gea Brande.
He's leading a demon army to overthrow the capital.
Oh, Rosalie's in trouble.
There is simply no time left to spare.
So you must return to Gea Brande at once.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll go right now.
I mean, hurry, but you still have time to take a bath, I'm sure.
Perhaps it's your long journey, but you smell a touch, Gaini.
Whoa, Rista, what's going on with your skin?
Oh, a sunburn.
I'm just a delicate, sweet-smelling little flower after all.
I don't stink!
I can't stink!
I will never stink again!
Well, enough about me.
How did Mosh and Elu-Lu's training go?
Excellent.
You're in for a big surprise.
He has mastered his metamorphosis, and she was able to upgrade her haste spell to Quick.
I'm very proud of both of them.
We have been working our tails off here.
We want to help Seiya as much as we can.
Wow, that's awesome.
You guys are great.
We couldn't have done it without Arya to teach us.
Yeah, thank you so much.
Alrighty, then.
I gotta get my butt in gear so these Rugrats don't show me up.
I'll prove to Seiya I'm more than just a pretty face.
Excuse me!
Coming in!
Ah!
Wait, wait, wait!
I knew you two were playing around earlier, but you're really not supposed to be doing this!
Put some other pants on now!
Once again, you don't get it.
We're just training in here.
Oh, can you blame me?
What's the point of having a beefcake around if you can't grab yourself a slice?
But still, hot, sweaty, sweet relations between a goddess and a mortal is forbidden!
Ugh.
You have no clue how things work around here.
This is why I can't stand novices.
I may not have much, but I am trying as hard as I possibly can.
I've been working like crazy all day to make this so I can help Seiya!
What is that thing?
Some kind of gross doll?
Was it in the trash?
Looks like it was woven out of oily golden thread.
Wait, you gotta be kidding me!
Did you...
I sure did!
I made this doll out of hair that I pulled out of my own head!
And I've dubbed her...
You're out of your damn mind!
I figured it would come in handy for Seiya's synthesis skill!
So I yanked them out in little clumps!
It hurts so bad, but worth it!
The level of psychotic just doesn't work for me.
I won't squeeze your boobs again.
Hey, Rista, you feeling okay?
I don't really think this is a great look for you.
I just thought this would help Seiya when he needs it.
But now that I stop and look at it, this is restraining order level crazy!
I'm sorry!
Stop it, it's disgusting.
Don't leak it on me.
I just want you to like me!
Seiya, how can I make you like me?
Cleaning up your snot would help.
But why, out of all of the goddesses here, would you choose that old ugly pain freak over me?
That was just Valkyrieja training.
Remember, I told you that you didn't understand what was going on.
You cross your heart and swear to God you mean that?
That is so stupid.
You are a god.
Okay, then.
It's pretty unbelievable.
But still, I trust you.
Mosh, put this item in my bag.
Sure, if you say so.
Well, anyway, did you get enough training?
Oh, yeah.
What about you, Master?
Mm-hmm.
That's great news, because we've got to get back to Gabrande.
Apparently, the last Heavenly King is attacking the capital.
Okay, let's get going.
Looking back, I was just too worked up to notice.
But Seiya never said his catchphrase.
I'm perfectly prepared.
Don't let those creatures douse your courage.
Remember, what we're all fighting for today is the future of Rosegard!
Wow, it's turned into an all-out war.
We've been eagerly awaiting your arrival, hero.
The Heavenly King, Eraser Kaiser, has been marching his elite force of the Demon Lord's army towards our city walls.
The men who met them on the battlefront have been made to retreat in terror.
The fight has finally come to our doorstep.
So it's a do-or-die moment here.
Hmm.
That one gives off a completely different aura from the rest.
He's the one in charge.
Eraser Kaiser.
Besides our interdimensional stalker, he's the strongest enemy we've faced so far.
I challenge you to send your mightiest human to face me in battle.
Or are there only weaklings in your kingdom?
The War Master!
Show them all we need to!
This fight's as good as over, boys!
That guy's the greatest warrior in the capital?
Yeah.
He's kinda old, don't he think?
They sent out a dusty old fart.
I had asked for a fight, not a sacrifice.
Seiya, you need to go and help him!
Actually, I don't think I will.
Huh?
If it's a sacrifice you want, then that's what you'll get.
Witness the power of my evil six-mode!
Crushing Saint's Light.
Oh, what?
No way.
But you're just a human.
Not even a hero!
Whoa, crazy!
One-shot Grandpa!
Grandpa, reach me!
Purify with massive saint's life.
Now those are some stats!
A human can get up there.
Fair goddess, it is an honor to meet you at last.
If this old man has stolen your hero's thunder, I humbly ask forgiveness.
Oh, there's no need to apologize.
I'm actually extremely grateful to you for defeating that heavenly king.
That old dude is like a walking force of nature!
He took out that big six-armed monster thing like it was nothing!
If you can wield this kind of power, why aren't you joining the battle to take down the demon lord?
Long story.
Okay?
This can't be!
It's starting to happen again!
Please, clear the area now!
Get moving!
This guy is looking like death-eating a cracker.
Maybe he's sick and can't leave the capital.
This is his condition.
Our brave war master is infantilizing!
Huh?
Mommy!
I made Boom Boom in my diapy again!
Huh?
Please say it!
H cupoの出るALIかとステータスを
強さも不器用さも
キミは特別すぎたよ
魔法だって
解けない謎の横顔で
見つめた明日
We'll see you next time.